Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben and Jerry's flavors but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is baked Alaska. Bringing this one
back from the flavor graveyard. If you
guys want me to do more of these flavor
graveyard Ben & Jerry's flavors, I am
more than happy to do so. This one was
amazing. It is a vanilla base with a
white chocolate swirl and little mini
marshmallows. The full recipe will be
down below in the caption. All you have
to do is combine all the ingredients for
the base. Throw in the freezer for at
least 16 hours. Take it out, run under
hot water for 30 seconds to a minute and
then throw it in your creamy on the
lettuce setting. Once it's done, it will
probably come out a little bit powdery
like this. All you have to do is scrape
down the sides with a butter knife and
then you can go ahead and add your mix
in. So, we're using about 15 g of white
chocolate chips combined with 2 g of
coconut oil to create a melted white
chocolate that when frozen and mixed in,
turns into a perfect white chocolate
swirl. And then a few of these little
mini jetpuff marshmallows. Then you can
just throw it on the mixing setting and
you're basically done. I topped it with
a few more of these little mini
marshmallows. Also, a quick shout out to
the girl that's been commenting for me
to make this flavor for like 2 weeks
now. Persistence is